<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kingsclear First Nation</title>
    <description>Kingsclear First Nation is located along the Saint John River, approximately 15 km west of the City of Fredericton, New Brunwsick.

The registered population of the Kingsclear First Nation is approximately 981 members, with 692 members residing on-reserve.
</description>
    <link>http://www.kingsclear.ca/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://www.kingsclear.ca/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2015 19:10:49 -0300</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2015 19:10:49 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Employment Opportunity: Archaeological Field Worker</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;TransCanada Pipelines Limited in partnership with Stantec Consulting and Green Eagle Services is currently accepting applications from highly motivated, enthusiastic Indigenous candidates within New Brunswick interested in participating in its 2015 archaeological shovel testing program. The job advertisement and description are provided at the links below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/assets/news/2015/arch-field-assistant-job-advert.pdf&quot;&gt;Job advertisement&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;/assets/news/2015/arch-field-assistant-job-description.pdf&quot;&gt;Job description&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2015 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kingsclear.ca/2015/09/08/employment-archaeological-field-worker/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kingsclear.ca/2015/09/08/employment-archaeological-field-worker/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mactaquac Project Community Open House</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;On August 4, 2015 Kingsclear First Nation hosted NB Power for a community open house at the Wulastukw Elementary School. The event was well attended and provided attendees an opportunity to engage with NB Power subject matter experts on a number of topics related to the Mactaquac project.&lt;!--end-excerpt--&gt; The event included a number of different stations detailing topics such as; the three project options, the comparative environmental review process, the Aboriginal engagement program (including a booth focusing on youth engagement). A preview of the conceptual plans developed by KFN Chief and Council and our partners Dillon Consulting Limited and NB Power for improvements to the community shoreline was also presented. The attendees had an opportunity to provide input on each of the three project options proposed for the Mactaquac Hydroelectric Generating Station, as well as other thoughts on how to keep informed and be involved. Much of the details presented at the open house, as well as other project related information is available &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mactaquac.ca/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. The website also allows the opportunity for those interested to provide their email addresses for project related updates, as well as contact information for NB Power for project related inquiries.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2015 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kingsclear.ca/2015/08/06/mactaquac-open-house/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kingsclear.ca/2015/08/06/mactaquac-open-house/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Young Entrepreneurs Are Ready to Sell Their Maliseet Children&#39;s Book</title>
        <description>&lt;figure&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/news/2015/childrens-book-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Authors and JEDI&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;figcaption&gt;(Left to right) Megan Young-Jones, Baillie Sacobie, Theo Polchies, Bryan Harn (JEDI), Brooke Sacobie, Amber Solomon&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s been almost a year since JEDI first met some industrious First Nation students at George Street Middle School (GSMS) in Fredericton, NB. At that time, the students had started to write and illustrate a children’s book for the entrepreneurship program that GSMS participates in every year through The Learning Partnership.&lt;!--end-excerpt--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last week, the students celebrated the delivery of the first hard copies of their newly published book. The authors and illustrators of the book are Baillie Sacobie, Theo Polchies, Amber Solomon, and Brooke Sacobie, all from Kingsclear First Nation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their book, titled “Weyossisok” which means ‘little animals’ in the Woolastooqiyik language, is an early childhood picture book written in both Maliseet and English. The book features a few different animals that are important to the Maliseet culture and includes short sentences on each animal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;clear-photo&quot;&gt;“When we were in elementary school we didn’t have any good books that were First Nation books,” said Theo, “so we decided that we wanted kids to learn Maliseet and we decided to do a children’s book to help them learn.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/news/2015/childrens-book-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Book cover&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“This book is important because we don’t want our language to be lost or to fade,” said Baillie, “so we figured that if we just taught that basics that people would learn it and then they could pass it down.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Walter Paul, the student’s former Maliseet teacher at GSMS, was the main translator for the book, taking what the children had written in English and then translating it into Maliseet. Theo’s grandmother, Barb Atwin, also helped with the translation. Natalie Sappier, a local Aboriginal artist, helped the children with the book as well and gave them tips and suggestions for their illustrations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Megan Young-Jones, the first Nations literacy teacher at GSMS, has also been working with the students on this project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/news/2015/childrens-book-3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Maliseet children&#39;s book&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I’m very excited for the students because they have been putting in so much work for 2 years,” said Ms. Young-Jones. “I’m not their homeroom teacher so we would only have about 2 hours, on a good week, that we would work together. I’m very fortunate that our administration recognized how important this project was and all of the learning that was taking place. I just helped to guide them through the process of working together as a team. It’s supposed to be student-led so while I might offer a suggestion once in a while it’s up to them to debate whether they want to take my suggestion or if they want to go their own way. This can be hard as a teacher because sometimes you can see where they might be going astray and you really want to pull them back, but it’s really about them learning the process. Now that they have their product, they are able to go out and be celebrated for all of the work that they’ve done. That’s going to be fantastic for them.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JEDI has also played a part in helping to get this book completed. JEDI has a small fund which can be used to help small community/ group ventures. This fund was created using proceeds from the JEDI golf tournament in October 2014.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We didn’t really know how we were going to get the money for the book,” said Baillie. “We were going to ask the school and then we came across JEDI and they helped us out with a grant which provided the seed money.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bryan Harn, the Economic Development Officer at JEDI, has been mentoring the students throughout their project. He helped them to work on resumes, create a business plan for their book, and to fill out the application for the grant money.  He also invited them to JEDI’s last plenary in Moncton.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Working with Bryan has been wonderful,” said Ms. Young-Jones. “JEDI has been an amazing business partner for us to have. Bryan has been excellent working with the children. Going to the plenary event in Moncton was huge for them, I think they realized the potential they can have and it opened a lot of doors for where they can go in their future.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The students have big plans now that their book is ready.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We ordered 30 books with our seed money,” said Amber, “so we could see who would be interested in buying our book.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It was kind of like a starter pack to see if we could sell them,” said Baillie. “We didn’t want to order a lot of books and then not have people buying them.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The interest is already there for the books though. Tracey O’Reilly, the Kingsclear First Nation Education Director purchased some books on the first day they were available and several of the Kingsclear council members have expressed interest in buying books as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We’re targeting the whole District 18, Anglophone West District,” said Brooke. “We’re also focusing on selling them in Kingslcear, St Mary’s and Tobique.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We’re using the profit from the sale of our books to buy books for the school on the reserve in Kingsclear,” said Baillie. “We noticed that when we all went through there that they didn’t have many books so we want to help them get more books.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The experience has been great for the students. They learned a lot about building a business, creating a book, and have learned personal skills as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It was a really cool project and we learned a lot of skills,” said Brooke, “like how to do business plans and resumes, so it helped us out a lot.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I learned that you have to be persistent with stuff,” said Baillie. “If someone doesn’t answer your email you have to send it again and again. That was a good skill to learn. I also learned a lot of Maliseet because we said it over and over again for the recordings.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I’ve noticed a huge gain in their confidence and self-esteem, that’s the main thing,” said Ms. Young-Jones. “I’m very excited and proud of these students.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JEDI is also proud of these young entrepreneurs and we look forward to following their success and the success of their book.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People interested in purchasing the book can contact Ms. Young-Jones at George Street Middle School or contact Bryan Harn at JEDI.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2015 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kingsclear.ca/2015/05/11/maliseet-childrens-book/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kingsclear.ca/2015/05/11/maliseet-childrens-book/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A New Community Planning – Looking for Input</title>
        <description>&lt;h3 id=&quot;about-the-comprehensive-community-plan&quot;&gt;About the Comprehensive Community Plan&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kingsclear First Nation has initiated the process to update our 2004 Community Plan. We will be spending the next few months establishing our community’s collective goals and aspirations for the next 15-20 years. What will our community look like and be in 2030? How can we get there? This exciting visioning exercise will allow us to align plans and policies to fully realize Our Kingclear.&lt;!--end-excerpt--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There will be many opportunities to help shape our new Community Plan, including:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Community-wide survey&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Community open houses&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Youth activities&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Website updates&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;current-involvement-opportunity-planning-working-group&quot;&gt;Current Involvement Opportunity: Planning Working Group&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are currently seeking passionate, civic-minded volunteers to play a key role in the community planning process. We are looking for community members to sit on the volunteer Planning Working Group to provide further input and oversight to the project and ensure the planning process remains a community-driven process. This is an excellent volunteer opportunity for those who are passionate about the future of Kingsclear First Nation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If interested, leave your contact information with Melissa at the Band Hall front desk, or email our Community Planning Consultant, Stephen Stone, at &lt;a href=&quot;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;:&amp;#115;&amp;#115;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;&amp;#110;&amp;#101;&amp;#064;&amp;#100;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#108;&amp;#111;&amp;#110;&amp;#046;&amp;#099;&amp;#097;&quot;&gt;&amp;#115;&amp;#115;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;&amp;#110;&amp;#101;&amp;#064;&amp;#100;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#108;&amp;#111;&amp;#110;&amp;#046;&amp;#099;&amp;#097;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meetings will be held on a monthly basis throughout the planning process, unless otherwise stated. First meeting is tentatively scheduled for May 21st, 2015.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information contact Stephen Stone by email: &lt;a href=&quot;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;:&amp;#115;&amp;#115;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;&amp;#110;&amp;#101;&amp;#064;&amp;#100;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#108;&amp;#111;&amp;#110;&amp;#046;&amp;#099;&amp;#097;&quot;&gt;&amp;#115;&amp;#115;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;&amp;#110;&amp;#101;&amp;#064;&amp;#100;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#108;&amp;#111;&amp;#110;&amp;#046;&amp;#099;&amp;#097;&lt;/a&gt; or phone: (506) 444-8820 ext. 5150&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2015 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kingsclear.ca/2015/05/10/community-planning/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kingsclear.ca/2015/05/10/community-planning/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Employment Opportunity: Field Monitor</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Employment opportunity for NB Power: Field Monitor. &lt;a href=&quot;/assets/news/2015/employment-field-monitor.pdf&quot;&gt;Click here to view job listing&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2015 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kingsclear.ca/2015/04/30/employment-field-monitor/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kingsclear.ca/2015/04/30/employment-field-monitor/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mental Wellness Evaluation Web Survey</title>
        <description>&lt;h3 id=&quot;notice-to-community&quot;&gt;Notice to Community&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As you may know, the Office of Evaluation at Health Canada is leading an evaluation of the First Nations and Inuit Health Branch (FNIHB) Mental Wellness Programs. As one component of this evaluation (called a Program Cluster Evaluation), FNIHB is asking for feedback about how its Mental Wellness programs are working. FNIHB has contracted our company, Horizons Community Development Associates (&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.horizonscda.ca&quot;&gt;www.horizonscda.ca&lt;/a&gt;) to help with this work.&lt;!--end-excerpt--&gt; The purpose of this part of the evaluation is to better understand first, if/how these Mental Wellness programs integrate with other community-based programs and services, and second, if/how these programs affect mental wellness outcomes for individuals, families, and communities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are inviting community program staff, Chiefs/Mayors and Councils, program participants, and other community members that have participated in a Mental Wellness program and/or have received health support services from the Indian Residential Schools Residential Support Program (IRS RHSP) to participate in a survey. We anticipate that this survey will complement the IRS RHSP client satisfaction survey that took place in the fall of 2014.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your community has the opportunity to share the positive impact these programs may have had. You can submit stories, case studies, reports, newsletters, videos or any other medium to illustrate your community’s successes. There is a question at the end of the survey where you can let us know that you’re interested and we will follow-up with you. The survey was developed by a working group whose members included FNIHB Mental Wellness and Addictions Regional Coordinators, FNIHB headquarters staff, an Assembly of First Nations health representative, and Inuit Tapiriit Kanatami (ITK) staff. Throughout the process, working group members liaised with their Regional teams and co-management committees (or similar structures) to provide guidance around data collection processes that respect Ownership Control Access Possession (OCAP) principles and other community-specific processes/protocols. These include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;recognizing cultural protocols relevant to the Aboriginal communities involved in evaluation, community leaders will be consulted to obtain their consent prior to approaching community members individually;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;using culturally relevant evaluation methods that include, where appropriate, face to face focus groups with community level Program staff and participants recognizing a preference for oral and participatory methods;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;discussing anonymity, privacy, and confidentiality prior to the collection of data; and,&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;meaningful engagement of the Assembly of First Nations (AFN) and Inuit Tapiriit Kanatami (ITK) in the evaluation process, which includes providing an opportunity to review data collection methods and tools developed to collect community-level data, preliminary findings and a draft of the evaluation report.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your input will be held in the strictest confidence. We will combine your individual comments with all the other input we collect, and we will not use any names in the report. We will also remove anything in your comments that could identify you or your community. You may skip any questions you do not wish to answer. We will not tell FNIHB who participated, or which questions anyone answered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once the data are collected, we will develop national and regional summaries which will be shared with communities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The link to the web survey is:
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.horizonscda.ca/surveys/index.php/595144/lang-en&quot;&gt;www.horizonscda.ca/surveys/index.php/595144/lang-en&lt;/a&gt;
A French version is also available.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you do not have reliable access to the Internet please email us and we will send you a version of the survey that you can fax or email to us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please feel free to contact us via email or the telephone numbers below if you have any questions. Also please feel free to contact Lynn Kennedy with FNIHB (&lt;a href=&quot;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;:&amp;#108;&amp;#121;&amp;#110;&amp;#110;&amp;#046;&amp;#107;&amp;#101;&amp;#110;&amp;#110;&amp;#101;&amp;#100;&amp;#121;&amp;#064;&amp;#104;&amp;#099;&amp;#045;&amp;#115;&amp;#099;&amp;#046;&amp;#103;&amp;#099;&amp;#046;&amp;#099;&amp;#097;&quot;&gt;&amp;#108;&amp;#121;&amp;#110;&amp;#110;&amp;#046;&amp;#107;&amp;#101;&amp;#110;&amp;#110;&amp;#101;&amp;#100;&amp;#121;&amp;#064;&amp;#104;&amp;#099;&amp;#045;&amp;#115;&amp;#099;&amp;#046;&amp;#103;&amp;#099;&amp;#046;&amp;#099;&amp;#097;&lt;/a&gt; or 613-884-2484).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We look forward to your input.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Best wishes,&lt;br /&gt;
Jean Robinson-Dexter&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;:&amp;#106;&amp;#101;&amp;#097;&amp;#110;&amp;#064;&amp;#104;&amp;#111;&amp;#114;&amp;#105;&amp;#122;&amp;#111;&amp;#110;&amp;#115;&amp;#099;&amp;#100;&amp;#097;&amp;#046;&amp;#099;&amp;#097;&quot;&gt;&amp;#106;&amp;#101;&amp;#097;&amp;#110;&amp;#064;&amp;#104;&amp;#111;&amp;#114;&amp;#105;&amp;#122;&amp;#111;&amp;#110;&amp;#115;&amp;#099;&amp;#100;&amp;#097;&amp;#046;&amp;#099;&amp;#097;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
(902) 354-2397&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cari Patterson&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;:&amp;#099;&amp;#097;&amp;#114;&amp;#105;&amp;#064;&amp;#104;&amp;#111;&amp;#114;&amp;#105;&amp;#122;&amp;#111;&amp;#110;&amp;#115;&amp;#099;&amp;#100;&amp;#097;&amp;#046;&amp;#099;&amp;#097;&quot;&gt;&amp;#099;&amp;#097;&amp;#114;&amp;#105;&amp;#064;&amp;#104;&amp;#111;&amp;#114;&amp;#105;&amp;#122;&amp;#111;&amp;#110;&amp;#115;&amp;#099;&amp;#100;&amp;#097;&amp;#046;&amp;#099;&amp;#097;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
cari@horizonscda.ca&lt;br /&gt;
(902) 582-7940&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2015 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kingsclear.ca/health%20centre/2015/04/23/mental-wellness-survey/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kingsclear.ca/health%20centre/2015/04/23/mental-wellness-survey/</guid>
        
        
        <category>health centre</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Elephant Thoughts - Upcoming Education Outreach Programs</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/assets/news/2015/elephant-thoughts.pdf&quot;&gt;Elephant Thoughts - Upcoming Education Outreach Programs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2015 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kingsclear.ca/education/2015/04/19/elephant-thoughts/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kingsclear.ca/education/2015/04/19/elephant-thoughts/</guid>
        
        
        <category>education</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Kingsclear Education - 1st Council Update</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/assets/news/2015/1st-council-update.docx&quot;&gt;Kingsclear Education - 1st Council Update&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2015 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kingsclear.ca/education/2015/04/19/1st-council-update/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kingsclear.ca/education/2015/04/19/1st-council-update/</guid>
        
        
        <category>education</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>PSE Applications</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Applications for post-secondary education are now available and will be accepted until May 9th, 2015.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/assets/news/2015/pse-application.docx&quot;&gt;Application in .docx format&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;/assets/news/2015/pse-application.pdf&quot;&gt;Application in .pdf format&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kingsclear.ca/education/post%20secondary%20education/2015/01/19/pse-applications/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kingsclear.ca/education/post%20secondary%20education/2015/01/19/pse-applications/</guid>
        
        
        <category>education</category>
        
        <category>post secondary education</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Christmas for Kids</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/news/2014/xmas-for-kids.png&quot; alt=&quot;Christmas for Kids&quot; /&gt;
For those that are eligible for Christmas for Kids, you will be called on Monday December 22, 2014 for pick up at the band hall. We wish you all a very Merry Christmas and a Happy New Year.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2014 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.kingsclear.ca/2014/12/18/christmas-for-kids/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.kingsclear.ca/2014/12/18/christmas-for-kids/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
